字幕制作：葫  芦
尤特加人不会成为猎物
不交朋友
掠食万物
-尤特加法典
尤特加
母星
我感应到你了 哥
I sense you, brother.
躲在
Hiding...
你的斗篷后面
behind your cloak.
你该设法争取自己的斗篷了
It is time to earn yours.
你还是太小 对付不了我
Still too small to take me head on.
利用这个洞穴
Use the cave!
你凭着怒火对抗我
You fight with rage.
我跟父亲一样战斗
I fight like father.
你不是父亲 你是戴克
You are not father, you are Dek!
你要投降吗？
Do you yield?
做梦
Never!
很好
Good.
我还活着 哥
I'm still alive, brother.
你还有很多要证明
Still much to prove...
才能展现你的能耐
to show who you are.
我是尤特加战士
I am Yautja.
还不是
Not yet.
你要拿你的剑吗 酷威？
Are you holding your sword, Kwei?
不要
No.
拿起来
Pick it up!
你留着这个玩具？
You kept this toy?!
你记得当时的情况
You remember what happened...
我失去了我的尖牙
I lost my fang!
你救了我一命
And you saved my life.
你保护我
You protected me.
过来
Come here.
我帮你修好了
Fixed it for you.
别炸死自己
Don't blow yourself up.
今天你发誓
Today you make a vow...
就跟我们的祖先一样
as our ancestors did before you.
争取你在家族中的地位
To earn your place in the clan...
你必须选择你的猎物
you must choose your prey.
带它回家
Bring it home...
否则就别回来了
or never return.
等等 倒回去
Wait - Go back!
干纳星
Genna.
死亡星球
The death planet.
不死卡里斯克的家乡
Home of the un-killable Kalisk.
连父亲都怕它
Even father fears it.Even father fears it.
那卡里斯克就会是我的战利品
Then the Kalisk shall be my trophy.
父亲说我最弱
Father calls me the weakest...
所以我必须杀死最强的
so I must kill the strongest.
失败必死无疑
Failure means death.
那我不会失败
Then I will not fail.
我不许你去
I cannot allow it.
我发誓会成功
I make my vow.
I make my vow!
父亲
Father.
很荣幸欢迎你
I welcome you with honor.
为什么没搞定？
Why is it not done?
他值得一次猎杀的机会
He deserves a hunt.
他是我们家族的弱者
He is our clan's weakness...
弱者必须剔除
weakness must be culled.
他会带卡里斯克回家
He will bring home the Kalisk.
愚蠢
Foolishness.
他是窝囊废
He is a runt.
你该趁他睡觉时杀了他
You should have done it as he slept.
杀了他
Kill him!
现在动手
Now!
他死了才能荣耀我们
He will only honor us in death.
父亲
Father.
酷威？
Kwei?
勇敢一点 弟
Be brave, brother.
父亲
Father!
酷威
Kwei!!!
原谅弱者
To forgive weakness...
就是示弱
is to show weakness.
不 父亲 不要
No! Father, no!
拿你的剑
Get your sword!
酷威
Kwei!!!
发射程序已启动
Launch sequence initiated.
带它回家
Bring it home.
干纳星
带它回家
Bring it home.
为了酷威
For Kwei.
铁血战士
杀
戮
之
地
尤特加人
Yautja!
这样
Is this... Is this... Is this...
这样有比较好吗？
Is this better?
宇宙通用翻译 你听到尤特加语
Universal translation.
别人听到他们的语言
You hear Yautja,others hear their language...
天啊
Oh, boy.
这对你可不妙
This isn't great for you.
它会等那些针使你瘫痪
It waitsfor the needles to paralyze you.
再趁你动弹不得时吃掉你
Then eats youwhile you can't move.
我能帮你 但
I could help you, but...I need a hand.
我需要帮忙
, but...I need a hand.
尤特加人独自狩猎
Yautja hunt alone.
尤特加人虽然独自狩猎
Yautja might hunt alone
但也独自死去
but they die alone too.
卡里斯克
Kalisk.
你在猎杀卡里斯克
You're hunting the Kalisk.
最好跑快点
Gotta run faster.
毒性很快吧？
It happens fast, huh?
如果你有武器 我能用
If you had a weapon,you know, I could use it.
丢过来 我帮你弄到解药
Throw me that,and I can get you the antidote.
不要拉倒
Now or never.
你好
Hi.
应该会完好如初
Should be good as new.
毒液让它们开花
The venom makes them bloom.
也让它们成为方便的解药
Also makes thema handy antidote.
拉我一把吧？
How about a lift?
出发
Let's go.
客气点 先生
Excuse you, sir.
你的腿怎么了？
What happened to your legs?
我是合成人
I'm synthetic.
我是威兰汤谷企业
I was built and deployed
为了研究而开发及部署的
by the Weyland-YutaniCorporation for research.
他们的人类在这星球撑不了一天
Because their humans wouldn'tlast a day on this planet.
我们发现
We found that...
听着
Look...
许多尤特加人为了卡里斯克而来
Many Yautja have comefor the great Kalisk,
没有一个活下来
and none have survived it...
或在干纳星生存
or Genna.
我见过卡里斯克
I've seen the Kalisk.
我活了下来
I survived it.
以下是我的建议 你带着我
Here's my proposal:You take me along with you,
我带你去它的巢穴
and I'll guide you to its den.
到了之后 我得到我的腿
Once there, I get my legs,
你获得战利品
you get your trophy,
皆大欢喜 一言为定罗？
and everyone's a winner. Deal?
你见过卡里斯克？
You have seen the Kalisk?
对 我见过卡里斯克
Oh, yeah. I've seen the Kalisk.
好吧
Okay. Hmm.
祝你旅途顺心
Good luck with your journey.
我就 自己走自己的
I'm just gonna...go on my journey.
相信你会想出办法的
I'm sureyou'll figure something out.
嘿
Hey.
我已经证明我对你有用处
I've already shown youthat I can be useful to you.
用处
Useful...
就像工具？
like tool?
对 没错 像工具
Yes. Yes, exactly, like a tool.
在干纳星存活就得顺势而为
The only way to survive Gennais to work with it,
我知道怎么做
and I know how.
只要用对工具
And with the right tool...
你就能逮到卡里斯克
you could get the Kalisk.
你可以成为第一个
You could be the first.
我会利用你 工具
I will use you, tool.
你能叫我希
You may call me Thi... Whoa!
你好像比其他尤特加人娇小 你几岁？
You seem smaller than the otherYautja. How old are you?
你用什么嚼东西？
And what does the chewing?
你的外尖牙还是内牙？
Your outside fangsor your inside teeth?
你怎么称呼？
What should I call you?
我没被人扔过 好刺激
I've never been thrown before.What a... thrill!
你的船坠毁时飞多快？
How fast were you goingwhen your ship crashed?
比亚光速快吗？ 我们还没达到那个速度
Faster than sub-light speed? We haven't cracked that yet.
还有 那把电浆剑很有趣
Also, that plasma swordis interesting.
只有你们家族有吗？
Is it unique to your clan?
我该怎么叫你？
And what may I call you?
我称它们为雨蛇
I call these imbre anguis.
它们只想吃点心
They just want a snack.
用蜂蜜比用醋能抓到更多苍蝇
You catch more flies with honeythan you do with vinegar.
我不要苍蝇
Don't want flies.
掠食生物是我的专业领域
Predatory organisms aremy specific area of expertise.
我广泛研究尤特加族
I've studied Yautja extensively.It's an impressive culture.
它是个独特的文化
来 随便问 我都有答案
Here, ask me anything.I bet I have the answer.
真好笑
Very funny.
你还没说你的名字
And you still haven'ttold me your name.
我叫戴克
Name is Dek.
现在朝那边说话
Now talk that way.
好 没问题
Okay, sure.
好 倒回去 话说从头
Well, let's back upand start at the beginning.
干纳星在640亿周期前形成
Genna was formed64 billion cycles ago,
当时邻近星系中的一颗垂死红矮星
when a dying red dwarf starin a neighboring system...
真的好美
It's so beautiful.
困在这里这么久
After all the timeI've been stuck here,
这个景色还是看不腻
I never get tired of the view.
你在这里多久了？
How long have you been here?
我们两年前抵达干纳星 建造一座基地
Well, we arrived on Genna twoyears ago, and we built a base.
然后我在兀鹰巢里度过人生中
Then, I was inthe vulture's nest for the most exciting
最刺激的13天7小时43分2秒
13 days, seven hours, 43 minutes and two seconds of my life.
但我始终明白有人会来
But I always knewsomeone would come.
只是猜错了是谁
I was just wrong about who.
谁会来？
Who would come?
泰莎
Tessa.
我们团队完全由合成人组成
Our crew is made upentirely of synths.
但泰莎和我比较特别
But Tessa and I are special.
我们比其他人更敏感
We have a higher sensitivitythan the others.
敏感是弱点
Sensitivity is weakness.
敏感让我们能理解这星球上的生物
Sensitivity is what allows usto understand the creatures on this planet.
我们原本就是要协力合作
We were createdto work in tandem.
我专注在实验室里 泰莎在野外
Me, cooped up in the lab,Tessa out in the field.
直到那美妙的一天 泰莎让我与她同行
Until the wonderful dayTessa let me come with her.
我们在探索干纳星
We were exploring Genna.
接着卡里斯克攻击我们
And then the Kalisk attacked us.
害我一分为二 也拆散了我们
Separated me... and us.
我记得最后听到的声音
The last soundI remember hearing
是泰莎呼喊我的名字
was Tessa calling out my name.
向我伸出手
Reaching for me.
然后卡里斯克出现
Then the Kalisk.
我不知所措
I didn't know what to do.
我不肯相信她死了
But I refuseto believe she's dead.
气密舱
系统已连接
实验单位重启中...
受试者：泰莎
威兰汤谷生物武器部
状态查询
希亚
Thia, Thia,
Thia, Thia, Thia...
希亚
Thia, Thia, Thia, Thia.
Thia, Thia.
状态：受损
核心功能：可用
任务未完成
首要任务仍然是：
- 获取
XX0522
样本
- 确保取回生物武器
注意
注意：侦测到新生命型态
物种：尤特加人
对任务有潜在威胁
你好 泰莎
Hello, Tessa.
公司并不满意
The Company is not pleased.
持续失败将导致你退役
Continued failure will resultin your decommission.
希亚在哪里？
Where's Thia?
尤特加人带走希亚
The Yautja has Thia.
我必须吃东西
I must eat.
两名战士 戴克与希亚 狩猎中
Two warriors.Dek and Thia, on the hunt.
问一下 我该做什么？
Quick question. What should I be doing?
这是什么生物？
What is this creature?
骨野牛 它们是卡里斯克的食物
Bone bison.They're Kalisk food.
那也会是我的食物
Then it will be my food, too.
好刺激 跟尤特加人一起狩猎
So exciting.Hunting with a Yautja.
泰莎绝对不相信
Tessa wouldn't believe it.
警告你一下
Just a warning...
给我安静
Quiet tool!
剃刀草
Razor grass.
会把你割成肉条 我们绕过去
It'll cut you to ribbons.We'll just go around.
你太容易放弃了
You give up too easily.
这趟狩猎恐怕不只有我们
We might not be alonein this hunt.
好奇怪的小动物 我没见过你
What an odd critter. I've never seen you before.
我是希亚 你好
Thia. Nice to meet you.
看来你的竞争对手比较
Looks like your competitionis better...
小心这些树上有月虫
Careful up in these trees.There are Luna bugs!
从你后面来了
Coming up behind you!
别小看它
Stronger than it looks!
戴克？
Uh, Dek?
戴克 你看
Dek! Look!
卡里斯克？
Kalisk?
不是卡里斯克
Not a Kalisk.
这个就是月虫
This is a Luna bug!
有其他武器吗？
Have any other weapons?
怎么停下来？ 快闪人
Why'd you stop? Let's get out of here.
你太容易放弃了
You give up too easily.
那是我参与过最棒的狩猎
That was the best huntI've ever been on.
我们是梦幻队伍
This is the dream teamright here.
超杀三人组 超杀三小队 超杀三巨头
The Dynamic Three.The Dynamic Trio. The Dynamic Tree-
三巨头 记得我们从树上掉下来吗？
Tree- Remember whenwe went down the tree?
那头怪兽的嘴
That monster's mouth, I mean...
味道不好闻 不过
Didn't smell great,didn't smell great. But...
我们击败它 搞定它 然后遇见你
We got him. We got him.And then we met you,
我们的小可爱
our little sweet,little, little thing.
真的 谢谢你给我这次经验
Thank you, seriously,for that experience.
真不可思议 超刺激
Truly amazing. Thrilling.
好刺激 你最喜欢哪个部分？
Truly thrilling.What was your favorite part?
我用剑刺进它的头
When I pierced its head with my sword,
它的血从我脸上滚滚流下
and its blood rushed down my face.
酷
Cool.
谢了 我不吃东西 但这样好甜蜜喔
No, thanks. I don't eat,but that's very sweet.
这种肉并不甜
This flesh is not sweet.
知道了
Good to know.
我们的小朋友好像饿了
Our little bud herelooks hungry.
我想它是把你当成自己人
I think she's marking you.
它要你成为它家族的一员
She wants youto be a part of her clan.
说不定它迷路了
Maybe she's lost.
我没有家族
I have no clan!
什么意思 尤特加人没家人吗？
What do you mean?Don't all Yautja have family?
没家族
No clan.
从来没人关照你吗？
So you never had anyonelooking out for you?
我曾经有一个哥哥
I had a brother.
曾经？
Had?
他怎么了？
What happened to him?
父亲杀了他
Father killed him.
你正在悲痛中
You're grieving.
悲痛是弱点
Grief is weakness.
你失去哥哥才来这里
You're herebecause you lost your brother.
我为了卡里斯克而来
I am here for Kalisk.
你为什么来这里？
Why are you here?
因为与你同行是回去找泰莎最好的办法
I'm herebecause traveling with you is the best wayto get back to Tessa.
我在兀鹰巢时 好怕再也见不到她
When I wasin that vulture's nest, I was so afraidI would never see her again.
你自己应该活得下去
You should be able to survive on your own.
我能靠自己生存
I can survive on my own.
但谁会想自己活下去？
But who would wantto survive on their own?
泰莎是你的姊妹
Tessa is your sister.
姊妹
Sister.
对
Yeah.
我想是吧
I guess she is.
我有 一个姊妹
I have... a sister.
好动人的想法
What a lovely thought.
我必须找到她
I need to find her.
还有腿
And legs.
你说什么？
Excuse me?
找到你的姊妹
Find your sister.
还有你的腿
And legs.
这是笑话吗？
Was that a joke?
太阳出来了
The sun rises.
走吧
Let's go.
我们不能丢下小巴
We can't leave Bud.
小巴？
Bud?
对 小巴 我帮它取了名字
Yeah, Bud. I named her.
尤特加人单独狩猎
Yautja hunt alone.
才怪 我陪着你
You're not alone, I'm with you.
你是工具
You're a tool.
要是没有它 那棵树会吃了我们
The tree would have eaten uswithout her.
现在我们不在树上
We're not in the tree now.
卡里斯克？
Kalisk?
它在这里喝水
It drinks here.
它在这里喝水？
It drinks here?
你不说话就成了没用的工具
You are a useless tool if you don't speak.
小巴救了我们
Bud saved us.
它吐你口水代表你是它家人
She spit on you to claim youas part of her family.
你父亲为何杀你哥？
Why'd your fatherkill your brother?
我哥想保护我
My brother was protecting me.
家族不能有弱者
The clan can have no weakness.
我会展现力量给他们看
I will show them strength.
在地球上
On Earth...
有种掠食动物叫狼
there's a predator knownas the wolf.
是一种强大的动物
It's a powerful creature.
它们成群狩猎
They hunt in packs.
忠心耿耿
They're very loyal.
狼群领袖是头狼
The leader of the packis the alpha.
是最强势的
Known as the most dominant.
狼
Wolf.
头狼一定是厉害的杀手
This alpha must be a great killer.
我也会猎杀它 -不
I will hunt it too. -No.
头狼不是最会杀戮的
The alpha isn't the wolfwho kills the most.
头狼其实是最能保护狼群的
The alpha is actually the onewho best protects the pack.
我懂了
I see...
但我将是最会杀戮的头狼
But I will be the alphathat kills the most.
卡里斯克的巢穴？
The Kalisk's den?
他们是谁？
Who are they?
威兰汤谷合成人
Weyland-Yutani synths.
卡里斯克摧毁我们大半个任务团队
The Kalisk destroyedmost of our mission team.
找到我了
There I am.
现在走路比较轻松了
Easier to walk now.
快了
It's about to be.
不是
No.No.
现在我走路比较轻松了
Easier for me to walk now.
当然 对
Of course. Right.
谢谢你 戴克
Thank you, Dek.
我不会忘记的
I'm never gonna forget this.
我也会记得
I too will remember this...
今天我成为尤特加战士戴克
today I become Dek of the Yautja.
我会表扬酷威
I will honor Kwei...
等我带卡里斯克回家
when I bring the Kalisk home.
然后尝到复仇的滋味
Then I taste revenge.
你会抢先看见我的战利品
You will be the first to see my trophy.
那对你来说是
It is a great honor.
莫大的荣幸
For you.
戴克 我得告诉你一件事
Dek, there's somethingI have to tell you.
你必须离开了
You need to leave now.
定位信标已激活
Location beacon activated.
什么？
What?
信标已激活
我通知泰莎 公司快过来了
I called Tessa.The company is on its way.
他们抵达时你不能在这里
You can't be herewhen they arrive.
我是来找卡里斯克的
I came here for the Kalisk.
我也是 戴克
So did I, Dek.
公司派我们来逮捕卡里斯克
The company sent us hereto capture the Kalisk.
你要我的战利品
You want my trophy.
卡里斯克在哪？
Where is the Kalisk?
戴克 你不能杀它
Dek, you can't kill it.
我利用你 工具 不是你利用我
I use you, tool. You do not use me!
抱歉 你该走了
I'm sorry. You have to leave.
我需要你帮忙带我过来
I needed youto help bring me here.
是我利用你
I use you!
卡里斯克在哪里？
Where is the Kalisk?
我是在帮你 戴克
I'm trying to help you, Dek.
你想你哥救你是为了让你死在这里吗？
You think your brothersaved your life just so you could die here?
那我会死得很光荣
Then my death will be honorable.
通知你的姊妹
Call your sister.
谁都不能阻止我
None can stop me.
拜托
Ugh! Come on!
戴克
Dek!
救你自己 工具
Save yourself, tool!
工具 帮我解开
Tool, get these off!
你不是希亚
You are not Thia.You are not Thia.
放开我
Release me!
你也是一个损坏的工具
You are another broken tool!
尤特加族会剔除弱者 你怎么没事？
The Yautja cull their weak.Why were you spared?
拿掉这些东西
Remove these!
否则我扯烂你脊椎 压碎你头颅
Or I'll rip out your spineand crush your skull!
我看过希亚的日志
I read Thia's logs.
你没跟她说过你哥为何保护你
You never told herwhy your brother protected you.
你什么都不是 只是一台装置
You are nothing. A device.
别人制造你 把你当打手
Made by others to do their work for them.
没错
That's correct.
你现在是威兰汤谷企业的资产
And you are now property of theWeyland-Yutani Corporation.
对你来说 是莫大的荣幸
It is a great honor. For you.
泰莎
Tessa.
你赶来了
You made it.
我们赶来了
We made it.
我见到好多事情
I've seen so much.
我有好多话要告诉你
I have so much to tell you.I saw such incredible creatures.
我看到惊人的动物
尤特加人是超棒的旅伴
The Yautja is a greattravelling companion.
希亚 关于卡里斯克你说得对
Thia.You were right about the Kalisk.
你背叛我
You betrayed me!
那只动物是再生奇蹟
The creatureis a regenerative miracle.
人类会感谢我们
Humanity will thank us.
我们抓到卡里斯克了？
We have the Kalisk?
对
Yes.
母亲会很高兴你多逮到一个
And Muthur will be pleasedwith your additional catch.
多逮到一个？
Additional catch?
尤特加人不是理想的样本
The Yautjais not an ideal specimen.
没错 不理想
No, not ideal.
但它的科技很有价值
But its technology is valuable.
我们能利用它的武器 丢下那个尤特加人
We can salvage its weaponsand leave the Yautja.
好主意
Good idea.
但它严重变形
But it's so malformed.
我们需要一个样本 用来研究
We're going to need a sample.For research.
他不是我们的任务目标
He was not the goalof our mission.
泰莎 他残缺不堪
Tessa, he is deficient.
泰莎
Tessa!
希亚 这是我们收到的要求
Thia,this is what is asked of us.
我们能超出他们的要求
We can be morethan what they ask of us.
我们能做什么？
What can we be?
当姊妹
Sisters.
希亚
Thia.
知道母亲为何给我们感情吗？
Do you know whyMuthur gave us feelings?
这样我们才能了解这星球的生物
So we could understandthe creatures on this planet.
好利用它们 -利用它们
- And exploit them.- Exploit them.
这个尤特加人不一样
The Yautja is different.
他救了我 就像你救了我
He rescued me.Like you rescued me.
我不是来这里救你的
I did not come hereto rescue you.
我是要完成任务
I am completing our mission.
第一次面对卡里斯克时
When we first faced the Kalisk,
我试图保护你
I tried to protect you.
那差点害我赔上一切
And that almost cost meeverything.
什么意思 泰莎？
What do you mean, Tessa?
我差点犯下跟尤特加人的哥哥一样的错
I almost made the same mistakethe Yautja's brother made.
弱者必须剔除
The weak must be culled.
希亚 你损坏了
And Thia, you're broken.
泰莎 母亲传来讯息
Tessa, incoming messagefrom Muthur.
逼这个尤特加人解释它的武器
Motivate the Yautjato explain its weapons.
这个单位呢？
And the unit?
把她装箱
Box her up.
亏我相信你
I trusted you.
我不喜欢这些工具
Don't like these tools.
对不起 我的姊妹
I'm sorry. My sister is -
我也不喜欢你的姊妹
Don't like sister either.
你怎么在说它的语言？
Why are you speakingits language?
跟工具说你在问装置的事
Tell tool you're asking about the device.
你听到命令了 我叫他解释这装置
You heard the orders. I'm asking itto explain this device.
这个装置是什么？
What is the device?
他在问这个装置
He's asking about the device.
小孩的玩具
It's a children's toy.
就说是地图
But say it's a map.
它说什么？
What did it say?
他说是地图
He says it's a map.
怎么用？
How does it work?
叫工具看里面
Tell tool to look inside.
那是小孩的玩具？
That was a toy for children?
尤特加小孩
Yautja children!
戴克 快跑
Run Dek!
快跑
Go... Go!
住手
Stop!
输入目的地座标 酷威
Enter destination coordinates, Kwei.
你救了我 哥
You saved me, brother.
狼
Wolf.
卡里斯克
Kalisk.
卡里斯克小孩
Kalisk child.
你好 母亲
Hello, Muthur.
泰莎
Tessa.
我们即将装载卡里斯克
We're about to load the Kalisk.
第一要务完成 标本已取得
Priority one complete.The specimen has been acquired.
谢谢你 泰莎
Thank you, Tessa.
我们真的在打造更好的世界
We truly are buildinga better world.
那个尤特加人的状况如何？
And what is the statusof the Yautja?
那个尤特加人是有缺陷的样本
The Yautjais a defective specimen.
那个尤特加人的状况如何？
What is the statusof the Yautja?
对不起 母亲 那个尤特加人死了
I'm sorry, Muthur.The Yautja is dead.
那他就不再是威胁
Then the Yautjais no longer a threat.
公司会很高兴
The Company will be pleased.
非常好
Nicely done.
集合
- Form up.
惨了
- Oh, shit.
干得好
Good job.
不要 动
Don't... move.
戴克 你怎么来了？
Dek! What are you doing here?
我来救你
I came to rescue you.
你回来救我？
You came back for me?
狼
Wolf.
你戴的这是什么？
What exactly are you wearing?
骨野牛
Bone Bison.
尤特加战士戴克
Dek of the Yautja.
还不是
Not yet...
希亚
Thia.
我们得快点 他们随时会有人来
We need to hurry. More of them will be hereany minute.
你怎么在这里？
What are you doing here?
谢了 小巴 我不用
Thanks, Bud. I'm good.
该走了
We need to go.
卡里斯克
Kalisk!
你还在想 戴克？
Still, Dek?
卡里斯克小孩
Kalisk child!
小巴？
Bud?
他们抓走了它母亲
They have her mother!
小巴是它的小孩？
Bud's its child?
有什么打算？
What's the plan?
你释放卡里斯克
You free the Kalisk.
我拿到战利品
I get my trophy.
你有20分钟启动发射
You have 20 minutesto initiate launch.
我们去打猎吧
Let's go hunt.
在这里等
Wait here.
你进去的话太显眼了
You roll in there,you're not exactly gonna fit in.
我有个点子
I have an idea.
我看到他了 跟我来
I see him. On me.
已锁定
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
你来做什么？ 我叫你去抓尤特加人
What are you doing here? I told you to get to the Yautja.
你说让船准备在20分钟后起飞
You said to prepare the shipfor take off in 20 minutes.
那你来干什么？ 我已经给你下令了
Then what are you doing here? I gave you an order.
那只动物怎么处置？
What should we doabout the creature?
什么动物？
What creature?
你该听她的
You should listen to her.
我该听她的？
I should listen to her?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们需要他的眼睛
We need his eyes.
戴克 被猎捕到的感觉如何？
Hi, Dek.How does it feel to be hunted?
你说呢
You tell me.
这就是你的计划？
This is the plan, yeah?
泰莎
Tessa.
被我自己的姊妹 背叛
Betrayed by my own... sister.
我们不是姊妹
We are not sisters.
这不是你的
That's not yours.
尤特加战士戴克
Dek of the Yautja.
还不是
Not yet.
你是来复仇的吗？
You've come here for revenge?
我是为了我的斗篷而来
I've come for my cloak.
这是什么？
What is this?
我完成猎杀行动了
I've completed my hunt.
那是我的战利品
That is my trophy.
你让我们家族蒙羞
You disgrace our clan...
酷威也是
And so did Kwei.
干掉他
Get rid of him.
或许活下来的儿子确实比较强
Perhaps the right son did survive.
马上投降
Yield now...
就能获得你在我们家族中的地位
and take your place in our clan.
我有自己的家族
I have my own clan.
斗篷终于到手了
Finally earned that cloak.
尤特加战士戴克
Dek of the Yautja.
铁血战士
杀
戮
之
地
又是你朋友？
More friends of yours?
不
No.
是我母亲
It's my mother.
字幕制作：葫  芦        Q群：491019388